Get the men with their plan right here, bring it swag with a man right here, leave it up
on sipping on beer, yeah clap for me men right here, get the men with their plan right here,
bring it swag with a man right here, leave it up on sipping on beer, yeah clap for me men right here
Hey... no matter what they say, The Master the blaster
Hey... no matter what they do, He is the master the blaster
get the men with their plan right here, bring it swag with a man right here, leave it up on sipping on beer, yeah clap for me men right here,
Got the men with the flag right here
Bring it swag with a man right here
Drip it, leaning up and sipping on here
Yeah, clap for me man right here
Sound your life
Yeah, give it up for my man JD
Setting fire to the street
Big up to man, big up to all ya lovely people